contec.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy | CONTEC

## Privacy Policy

CONTEC respects your privacy and rights relating to your personal information.  
You don't have to provide any personal information when you visit CONTEC global corporate website (the site). However, you may want to contact us online – to ask a question, to learn more about our products, or to ask for specific information about CONTEC or its service. If you choose to contact CONTEC online, you will find our online forms ask for common types of personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, or country you live in. We ask for this type of information to help us to respond to your inquiry or request.

At CONTEC, we use the following guidelines to protect your information we collect during your visit to our website (www.contec.com).

### 1\. Obtaining Your Personal Information

When we ask you to provide us with your personal information, we advise you of the purpose of using such information and obtain your prior consent.

### 2\. Using Your Personal Information

CONTEC does not use your personal information for any other purposes than that you approved previously. CONTEC may use such information to communicate with you about our new products, technical support and event information.

### 3\. Sharing or Disclosing Your Personal Information with/to Third Parties

CONTEC does not share or disclose your personal information with or to any Third Parties except:

  * when you have given us prior consent,
  * when the disclosure is requested by a judicial or governmental agency.

When CONTEC transfers your Personal information to its agents, affiliates or partners, CONTEC enters an agreement on Personal Information Protection between its agents, affiliates or partners and requires that such agent, affiliate or partner handle your Personal information with the same concern for personal privacy as CONTEC.

### 4\. Protecting Your Personal Information

CONTEC takes necessary and appropriate steps to protect your personal information from loss, destruction, leakage, damage and illegal access. CONTEC stores your personal information on password-protected, access-controlled servers to which no authorized personnel are allowed to access.

### 5\. About the Use of Cookies and Access Logs

A cookie is a small text file that a website places on your computer. CONTEC uses cookies to recognize repeat visits to the site, to facilitate the site's navigation and to improve your experience at CONTEC website.  
We also use access logs that automatically collect information such as your IP address, the locale, language, country, the browser you are using, the web page from which you came, and a record of your activity on the site. We use those information to learn general trends in traffic pattern so that we can further improve our website.

### 6\. Contacting CONTEC about Your Personal Information

You can opt out at any time to the use of your personal information for direct communication purpose via e-mail, fax, phone or mail.  
You may contact us at [pm.office@jp.contec.com](mailto:pm.office@jp.contec.com) asking for review of data we obtained, correction or update thereof, deletion of your personal information or cancellation of your previously given consent to us. Upon such request, CONTEC takes an appropriate action accordingly.

## Policy Updates

CONTEC reserves the right to update this policy based on changes of social requirement and amendments of laws and regulations. CONTEC discloses its Privacy Policy at the corporate web site so that you can review it at any time you want to.

Updated: May 10, 2011  
CONTEC Co., Ltd.
